<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<items>
	<item>The main activities in construction are detailed design, coding, debugging, integration and developer testing</item>
	<item>Your understanding of how to do construction determines how good a programmer you are</item>
	<item>Care about your craft</item>
	<item>Think! About your work. Constantly be thinking, critiquing your work in real time.</item>
	<item>Every day, work to refine the skills you have and to add new tools to your repertoire.</item>
	<item>Don't live with broken windows.</item>
	<item>Bad code requires lots of comments.</item>
	<item>Outdated comments are worse than no comments at all.</item>
	<item>Don't forget TESTABILITY</item>
	<item>Pragmatic Programmers get the job done, and do it well.</item>
	<item>An investment in knowledge always pays the best interest</item>
	<item>Favor object composition over class inheritance</item>
	<item>The overarching goal of preparing for construction is risk reduction.</item>
	<item>Mythical Man-Month software scheduling: 1/3 planning, 1/6 coding, 1/4 testing, 1/4 system-integration testing</item>
	<item>Great software today is often preferable to perfect software tomorrow</item>
	<item>Invest regularly in your knwoledge portfolio</item>
	<item>SOLID means Single responsability, Open/close, Liskov substitution, Interface segregation, Dependency inversion</item>
	<item>Provide options, don't make lame excuses</item>
	<item>ASCII is able to represent every character using a number between 32 and 127. Space is 32, the letter “A” is 65, etc. This could conveniently be stored in 7 bits</item>
	<item>Unicode was a brave effort to create a single character set that included every reasonable writing system on the planet and some make-believe ones like Klingon, too.</item>
	<item>In UTF-8, every code point from 0-127 is stored in a single byte.</item>
	<item>It does not make sense to have a string without knowing what encoding it uses.</item>
	<item>It’s harder to read code than to write it.</item>
	<item>When you throw away code and start from scratch, you are throwing away all that knowledge. All those collected bug fixes. Years of programming work.</item>
</items>