<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<items>
	<item>Do your best and forget the rest</item>
	<item>Stay flexible</item>
	<item>Find your purpose</item>
	<item>Have a plan</item>
	<item>No more zero days</item>
	<item>Always do something for your goals</item>
	<item>VARIETY Is the Spice of . . . Everything</item>
	<item>CONSISTENCY Reigns Supreme</item>
	<item>Love it or leave it</item>
	<item>Get Real</item>
	<item>Find a Balance</item>
	<item>The Three R’s: Recharge, Recover, Relax</item>
	<item>Be grateful to the three you’s</item>
	<item>Forgive yourself</item>
	<item>Exercise and read books</item>
	<item>Take your time</item>
	<item>Be GRATEFUL to the past you for the positive things you’ve done.</item>
	<item>Find friends to workout</item>
	<item>Have fun. Exercising should be fun.</item>
	<item>Finding passion in fitness is crucial to enjoying yourself while attaining amazing results.</item>
	<item>The more you do, the better you get</item>
	<item>Make exercising a lifelong habit</item>
	<item>Choose training techniques that take you out of your comfort zone</item>
	<item>Focus on your weaknesses</item>
	<item>Variety will help prevent boredom and injuries</item>
	<item>Turn up the volume. More is better; more reps, more weight, and more resistance.</item>
	<item>More intensity does NOT equate to a miserable experience</item>
	<item>Tiny increments over time will not only improve your fitness, but it will also dramatically improve your physique.</item>
	<item>Find the yin. Sleeping, massage, meditation, and stress management etc., are the cornerstone of a fit and healthy lifestyle.</item>
	<item>The discipline of training intensely, also requires the discipline of taking the time to heal and recover.</item>
	<item>Schedule all of your workouts in advance.</item>
	<item>Plan it, and you’ll do it</item>
	<item>You can do ANYTHING you set your mind to</item>
	<item>Are you tough enough for ASYLUM?</item>
	<item>What would you do if you weren't afraid?</item>
	<item>Worry is a misuse of imagination</item>
	<item>Everything starts with you. The way you feel, your motivation, how happy you are. It all beings with you.</item>
</items>
