<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<quotes>
	<quote source="Kurt Vonnegut">
Another flaw in the human character is that everyone wants to build and 
nobody wants to do maintenance.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Dr. Seuss">
Don't cry because it's over. Smile because it happened.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
Sex is like air; it is not important unless you aren't getting any.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Jake The Dog">
Sucking at something is the first step towards being sorta good at something.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Elbert Hubbard">
There is only one way to avoid criticism: Do nothing, 
say nothing, and be nothing.</quote>
	<quote source="George Bernard Shaw">
Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.
</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
The happiest people don't have the best of everything, they make the best 
of everything.
</quote>
	<quote source="Thich Nhat Hanh">
When another person makes you suffer, it is because he suffers deeply within 
himself, and his suffering is spilling over. He does not need punishment; 
he needs help. That's the message he is sending.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Churchill">If you're going through hell, keep going.</quote>
	<quote source="General Patton">
Remember men! The object about war is not to die for one's country! 
But to make the other bastard die for his!
	</quote>
	<quote source="Tyrion Lannister">
Never forget what you are, for surely the world will not. Make it your 
strength. Then it can never be your weakness. Armour yourself in it, 
and it will never be used to hurt you.		
	</quote>
	<quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
The problem with quotes on the Internet is that you can not verify them.
</quote>
	<quote source="Butters">
Well yeah, and I'm sad, but at the same time I'm really happy that something 
could make me feel that sad. It's like, it makes me feel alive, you know? 
It makes me feel human. And the only way I could feel this sad now is if I 
felt somethin' really good before. So I have to take the bad with the good, 
so I guess what I'm feelin' is like a, beautiful sadness.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Dr. Seuss">To the world you may be one person; but to one person you may be the world.</quote>
	<quote source="Bertrand Russell">
The trouble with the world is that the stupid are cocksure and 
the intelligent are full of doubt.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
Do not attribute to malice what can easily be explained by stupidity
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
Maturity begins when you can be right without having to prove the other 
person wrong.
	</quote>
	<quote source="A.A. Milne">
How lucky am I to have something that makes saying goodbye so hard.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
If you're the smartest person in the room, you're probably in the wrong room.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
You don't have to be better than everybody else, you just have to 
be better than you were a week ago.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
A year from now, you'll wish you would have started today.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
If you are good you'll tell everyone. If you are great people will tell you
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">The good 'ol days are starting right now.</quote>
	<quote source="Buddha">
Holding onto anger is like drinking poison and expecting the other person 
to die.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Glenn Turner">
Worrying is like a rocking chair, it gives you something to do, 
but it gets you nowhere.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Wayne Gretzky">You miss 100% of the shots you don't take.</quote>
	<quote source="Mahatma Gandhi">Be the change you wish to see in the world.</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
No man has the right to be an amateur in the matter of physical training. 
It is a shame for a man to grow old without seeing the beauty and strength
of which his body is capable.
	</quote>
	<quote source="NCFitClub">
Food is the most abused anxiety drug. 
Exercise is the most underutilized antidepressant.
	</quote>
	<quote source="George Halas">
Nobody who gave their best ever regretted it 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
Control your hormones, control your destiny.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Churchill">
Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue 
that counts.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Eleanor Roosevelt">
Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds 
discuss people.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Kevin Kruse">
Life isn’t about getting and having, it’s about giving and being
	</quote>
	<quote source="Albert Einstein">
Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Michael Jordan">
I’ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I’ve lost almost 300 games. 
26 times I’ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I’ve 
failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Amelia Earhart">
The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="W. Clement Stone">
Definiteness of purpose is the starting point of all achievement.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Mark Twain">
Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you 
didn’t do than by the ones you did do, so throw off the bowlines, sail away 
from safe harbor, catch the trade winds in your sails.  Explore, Dream, 
Discover.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Charles Swindoll">
Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Buddha">
The mind is everything. What you think you become.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Chinese Proverb">
The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Woody Allen">
Eighty percent of success is showing up.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Stephen Covey">
I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Pablo Picasso">
Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once he 
grows up. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Maya Angelou">
I’ve learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what 
you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.  
	</quote>
	<quote source="Zig Ziglar">
People often say that motivation doesn’t last. Well, neither does bathing.  
That’s why we recommend it daily. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Ralph Waldo Emerson">
The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
When you do things right, people won't be sure you've done anything at all.
	</quote>
	<quote source="George Addair">
Everything you’ve ever wanted is on the other side of fear.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Maimonides">
Teach thy tongue to say, “I do not know,” and thous shalt progress. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
You can’t fall if you don’t climb.  But there’s no joy in living your whole 
life on the ground.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Japanese Proverb">
Fall seven times and stand up eight.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Les Brown">
Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Joshua J. Marine">
Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes 
life meaningful.
	</quote>
	<quote source="George Eliot">
It is never too late to be what you might have been.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Vincent van Gogh">
I would rather die of passion than of boredom.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Anonymous">
A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Ann Landers">
It is not what you do for your children, but what you have taught them to do
 for themselves, that will make them successful human beings.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Confucius">
It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Norman Vaughan">
Dream big and dare to fail.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Tony Robbins">
If you do what you’ve always done, you’ll get what you’ve always gotten.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Mae Jemison">
It’s your place in the world; it’s your life. Go on and do all you can 
with it, and make it the life you want to live.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Eleanor Roosevelt">
Remember no one can make you feel inferior without your consent. 
	</quote>
	<quote source="Grandma Moses">
Life is what we make it, always has been, always will be.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
It’s not the years in your life that count. It’s the life in your years.
	</quote>
	<quote source="William Morris">
The true secret of happiness lies in taking a genuine interest in all the details of daily life.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Mary Manin Morrissey">
Even though you may want to move forward in your life, you may have one foot on the brakes. In order to be free, we must learn how to let go. Release the hurt. Release the fear. Refuse to entertain your old pain. The energy it takes to hang onto the past is holding you back from a new life. What is it you would let go of today?
	</quote>
	<quote source="Bruce Lee">
Do not pray for an easy life, pray for the strength to endure a difficult one
	</quote>
	<quote source="Oscar Wilde">
Everything in moderation, including moderation.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Mike Murdoch">
The secret of your future is hidden in your daily routine.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Maurice Chevalier">
Old age is not so bad when you consider the alternatives.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Philip Sidney">
Either I will find a way, or I will make one.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Thomas Edison">
Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Samuel Beckett">
Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better.
	</quote>
	<quote source="CS Lewis">
You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Albert Einstein">
You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Confucius">
Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Jimmy Dean">
I can't change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Viktor Kiam">
Even if you fall on your face, you're still moving forward.
	</quote>
	<quote source="George S. Patton">
Accept the challenges so that you can feel the exhilaration of victory.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Cicero">
Live as brave men; and if fortune is adverse, front its blows with brave hearts.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Milton Berle">
A committee is a group that keeps minutes and loses hours.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Eminem">
The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Socrates">
Beware the barrenness of a busy life.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Harvey Fierstein">
Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life; define yourself.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Bil Keane">
They invented hugs to let people know you love them without saying anything.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Robin Williams">
You're only given a little spark of madness. You mustn't lose it.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Steve Jobs">
Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Arnold Schwarzenegger">
Strength does not come from winning. Your struggles develop your strengths. When you go through hardships and decide not to surrender, that is strength.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Hal Borland">
Knowing trees, I understand the meaning of patience. Knowing grass, I can appreciate persistence.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Peter Drucker">
The most important thing in communication is hearing what isn't said.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Lawrence Clark Powell">
Write to be understood, speak to be heard, read to grow.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Albert Einstein">
Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Gilbert Parker">
There is no influence like the influence of habit
	</quote>
	<quote source="Ralph Marston">
What you do today can improve all your tomorrows.
	</quote>
	<quote source="Brian Tracy">
I've found that luck is quite predictable. If you want more luck, take more chances. Be more active. Show up more often.
	</quote>
</quotes>

