<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<quotes>
  <quote source="Kurt Vonnegut">
    Another flaw in the human character is that everyone wants to build and
    nobody wants to do maintenance.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dr. Seuss">
    Don't cry because it's over. Smile because it happened.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    Sex is like air; it is not important unless you aren't getting any.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jake The Dog">
    Sucking at something is the first step towards being sorta good at something.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Elbert Hubbard">
    There is only one way to avoid criticism: Do nothing,
    say nothing, and be nothing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George Bernard Shaw">
    Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    The happiest people don't have the best of everything, they make the best
    of everything.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Churchill">If you're going through hell, keep going.</quote>
  <quote source="General Patton">
    Remember men! The object about war is not to die for one's country!
    But to make the other bastard die for his!
  </quote>
  <quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
    The problem with quotes on the Internet is that you can not verify them.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dr. Seuss">To the world you may be one person; but to one person you may be the world.</quote>
  <quote source="Bertrand Russell">
    The trouble with the world is that the stupid are cocksure and
    the intelligent are full of doubt.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    Do not attribute to malice what can easily be explained by stupidity
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    Maturity begins when you can be right without having to prove the other
    person wrong.
  </quote>
  <quote source="A.A. Milne">
    How lucky am I to have something that makes saying goodbye so hard.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    If you're the smartest person in the room, you're probably in the wrong room.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    You don't have to be better than everybody else, you just have to
    be better than you were a week ago.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    A year from now, you'll wish you would have started today.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    If you are good you'll tell everyone. If you are great people will tell you
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">The good 'ol days are starting right now.</quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    Holding onto anger is like drinking poison and expecting the other person
    to die.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Glenn Turner">
    Worrying is like a rocking chair, it gives you something to do,
    but it gets you nowhere.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Wayne Gretzky">You miss 100% of the shots you don't take.</quote>
  <quote source="Mahatma Gandhi">Be the change you wish to see in the world.</quote>
  <quote source="NCFitClub">
    Food is the most abused anxiety drug. Exercise is the most underutilized antidepressant.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George Halas">
    Nobody who gave their best ever regretted it
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    Control your hormones, control your destiny.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Churchill">
    Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue
    that counts.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Eleanor Roosevelt">
    Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds
    discuss people.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Kevin Kruse">
    Life isn't about getting and having, it's about giving and being
  </quote>
  <quote source="Albert Einstein">
    Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Amelia Earhart">
    The most difficult thing is the decision to act, the rest is merely tenacity.
  </quote>
  <quote source="W. Clement Stone">
    Definiteness of purpose is the starting point of all achievement.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Charles Swindoll">
    Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    The mind is everything. What you think you become.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Chinese Proverb">
    The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Woody Allen">
    Eighty percent of success is showing up.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Stephen Covey">
    I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Pablo Picasso">
    Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once he
    grows up.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Maya Angelou">
    I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what
    you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Zig Ziglar">
    People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing.
    That's why we recommend it daily.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Ralph Waldo Emerson">
    The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    When you do things right, people won't be sure you've done anything at all.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George Addair">
    Everything you've ever wanted is on the other side of fear.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Maimonides">
    Teach thy tongue to say, "I do not know," and thous shalt progress.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    You can't fall if you don't climb.  But there's no joy in living your whole
    life on the ground.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Japanese Proverb">
    Fall seven times and stand up eight.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Les Brown">
    Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Joshua J. Marine">
    Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes
    life meaningful.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George Eliot">
    It is never too late to be what you might have been.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Vincent van Gogh">
    I would rather die of passion than of boredom.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
    A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Ann Landers">
    It is not what you do for your children, but what you have taught them to do
    for themselves, that will make them successful human beings.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Confucius">
    It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Norman Vaughan">
    Dream big and dare to fail.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Tony Robbins">
    If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always gotten.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Mae Jemison">
    It's your place in the world; it's your life. Go on and do all you can
    with it, and make it the life you want to live.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Eleanor Roosevelt">
    Remember no one can make you feel inferior without your consent.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Grandma Moses">
    Life is what we make it, always has been, always will be.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
    It's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years.
  </quote>
  <quote source="William Morris">
    The true secret of happiness lies in taking a genuine interest in all the details of daily life.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Mary Manin Morrissey">
    Even though you may want to move forward in your life, you may have one foot on the brakes. In order to be free, we must learn how to let go. Release the hurt. Release the fear. Refuse to entertain your old pain. The energy it takes to hang onto the past is holding you back from a new life. What is it you would let go of today?
  </quote>
  <quote source="Bruce Lee">
    Do not pray for an easy life, pray for the strength to endure a difficult one
  </quote>
  <quote source="Oscar Wilde">
    Everything in moderation, including moderation.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Mike Murdoch">
    The secret of your future is hidden in your daily routine.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Maurice Chevalier">
    Old age is not so bad when you consider the alternatives.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Philip Sidney">
    Either I will find a way, or I will make one.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Thomas Edison">
    Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Samuel Beckett">
    Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better.
  </quote>
  <quote source="CS Lewis">
    You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Albert Einstein">
    You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Confucius">
    Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jimmy Dean">
    I can't change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Viktor Kiam">
    Even if you fall on your face, you're still moving forward.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George S. Patton">
    Accept the challenges so that you can feel the exhilaration of victory.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Cicero">
    Live as brave men; and if fortune is adverse, front its blows with brave hearts.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Milton Berle">
    A committee is a group that keeps minutes and loses hours.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Eminem">
    The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Socrates">
    Beware the barrenness of a busy life.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Harvey Fierstein">
    Never be bullied into silence. Never allow yourself to be made a victim. Accept no one's definition of your life; define yourself.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Bil Keane">
    They invented hugs to let people know you love them without saying anything.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Robin Williams">
    You're only given a little spark of madness. You mustn't lose it.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Steve Jobs">
    Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Arnold Schwarzenegger">
    Strength does not come from winning. Your struggles develop your strengths. When you go through hardships and decide not to surrender, that is strength.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Hal Borland">
    Knowing trees, I understand the meaning of patience. Knowing grass, I can appreciate persistence.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Peter Drucker">
    The most important thing in communication is hearing what isn't said.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lawrence Clark Powell">
    Write to be understood, speak to be heard, read to grow.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Albert Einstein">
    Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Gilbert Parker">
    There is no influence like the influence of habit
  </quote>
  <quote source="Ralph Marston">
    What you do today can improve all your tomorrows.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Brian Tracy">
    I've found that luck is quite predictable. If you want more luck, take more chances. Be more active. Show up more often.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Marcus Aurelius">
    If you are distressed by anything external, the pain is not due to the thing itself, but to your estimate of it; and this you have the power to revoke at any moment.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Marcus Aurelius">
    Never let the future disturb you. You will meet it, if you have to, with the same weapons of reason which today arm you against the present.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Randy Pausch">
    Complaining does not work as a strategy. We all have finite time and energy. Any time we spend whining is unlikely to help us achieve our goals. And it won't make us happier.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
    It is the power of the mind to be unconquerable.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Nassim Nicholas Taleb">
    A Stoic is someone who transforms fear into prudence, pain into transformation, mistakes into initiation, and desire into undertaking.
  </quote>
  <quote source="H. Jackson Brown, Jr">
    The best preparation for tomorrow is doing your best today.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jimmy Dean">
    I can't change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.
  </quote>
  <quote source="William Shakespeare">
    We know what we are, but know not what we may be.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Maya Angelou">
    My mission in life is not merely to survive, but to thrive; and to do so with some passion, some compassion, some humor, and some style.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Aesop">
    No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dale Carnegie">
    Any fool can criticize, condemn, and complain but it takes character and self-control to be understanding and forgiving.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jean de La Bruyère">
    The pleasure of criticizing takes away from us the pleasure of being moved by some very fine things.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Aristotle">
    Criticism is something we can avoid easily by saying nothing, doing nothing, and being nothing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Norman Vincent Peale">
    The trouble with most of us is that we’d rather be ruined by praise than saved by criticism.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Unknown">
    Before you go and criticize the younger generation, just remember who raised them.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Steve Goodier">
    Who do you spend time with? Criticizers or encouragers? Surround yourself with those who believe in you. Your life is too important for anything less.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Winston Churchill">
    Criticism may not be agreeable, but it is necessary. It fulfills the same function as pain in the human body. It calls attention to an unhealthy state of things.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
    He has a right to criticize, who has a heart to help.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Marshall Mcluhan">
    There are no passengers on spaceship earth. We are all crew.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Douglas Coupland">
    There are three things we cry for in life: things that are lost, things that are found, and things that are magnificent.
  </quote>
  <quote source="J.K. Rowling">
    It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dr. Seuss">
    Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Ralph Waldo Emerson">
    Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could. Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day. You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Abraham Lincoln">
    If I have nine hours to cut down a tree, I would spend six hours sharpening my axe.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Albert Einstein">
    Anyone that has never made a mistake has never tried anything new
  </quote>
  <quote source="Mother Theresa">
    Some people come into your life as blessings. Other people come into your life as lessons.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dalai Lama">
    Don't let the behaviour of others destroy your inner peace.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    Those who are awake, live in a state of constant amazement
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lao Tzu">
    If you're depressed, you're living in the past. If you're anxious, you're living in the future. If you're at peace, you're living in the present.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dalai Lama">
    Old friends pass away, new friends appear. it's just like the days. An old day passes, a new day arrives. The important thing is to make it meaningful: a meaningful friend. A meaningful day.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    All that we're, is the result of what we've thought. The mind is everything. What we think, we become
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lao Tzu">
    When I let go of what I'm, I become what I might be
  </quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    Each morning, we're born again. What we do today is what matters most.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Thích Nhất Hạnh">
    Happiness is here. Now.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Buddha">
    Even death isn't to be feared by one who's lived wisely.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dalai Lama">
    When you think everything is someone else’s fault, you'll suffer a lot. When you realise that everything springs only from yourself, you'll learn both peace and joy.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Tilopa">
    Have a mind that's open to everything and attached to nothing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lao Tzu">
    Act without expectations.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Osho">
    Life begins where fear ends.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Chuang-Tzu">
    Flow with whatever may happen. Let your mind be free: Stay centered by accepting whatever you're doing. This is the ultimate.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Dogen Zenji">
    Prefer to be defeated in the presence of the wise than to excel among fools.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Thích Nhất Hạnh">
    To be beautiful means to be yourself. You don’t need to be accepted by others. You need to accept yourself
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lao Tzu">
    The journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Gandhi">
    You must be the change you wish to see in the world.
  </quote>
  <quote source="George Bernhard Shaw">
    A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Michel De Montaigne">
    He who fears he will suffer, already suffers because he fears.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Confucius">
    Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Mary Engelbreit">
    If you don’t like something, change it. If you can’t change it, change the way you think about it.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Viktor Frankl">
    Life is never made unbearable by circumstances, but only by lack of meaning and purpose.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Stephen Covey">
    Most people do not listen with the intent to understand; they listen with the intent to reply.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Joshua J. Marine">
    Challenges is what makes life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Oliver Wendell Holmes">
    A mind that is stretched by a new experience can never go back to its old dimensions.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Take time to know yourself. "Know thyself" said Aristotle. When you know who you are, you can be wise about your goals, your dreams, your standards, your convictions. Knowing who you are allows you to live your life with purpose and meaning.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Show up fully. Don't dwell on the past, and don't daydream about the future, but concentrate on showing up fully in the present moment.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Don't make assumptions. If you don't know the situation fully, you can't offer an informed opinion.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Be patient and persistent. Life is not so much what you accomplish as what you overcome.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    In order to get, you have to give. If you support, guide, and lead others, if you make contributions to their lives, you will reap the best rewards.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Luck comes from hard work. Luck happens when hard work and timing and talent intersect.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Be your best at all times. You never know what the future will bring, so always make the best use of the present.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Don't try to impress everyone. The unhappiest people are those who care the most about what other people think.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Don't be afraid of being afraid. Sometimes the one thing you need for growth is the one thing you are most afraid to do.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Listen to learn. Learn how to listen. You can't learn anything when you're talking.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Life's good, but it's not fair. The delusion that life's supposed to be fair is the source of much unhappiness.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    No task is beneath you. Don't put yourself above anyone or anything; work hard in silence and let success make the noise.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    You can't always get what you want. But, as the song says, if you try you may find you get what you need.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Don't make decisions when you are angry or ecstatic. The best decisions are made with a clear conscious mind, not in the throes of any emotion--positive or negative.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Don't worry what other people think. Personality begins where comparison leaves off. Be unique. Be memorable. Be confident. Be proud.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Use adversity as an opportunity. Every loss leads to an opportunity, and every adversity leads to new possibilities.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Do what is right, not what is easy. Strength of character leads us to do the right thing, even when there are easier options.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Dreams remain dreams until you take action. Without action, an idea is just a dream.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Treat others the way you want to be treated. Do right. Do your best. Treat others as you would want them to treat you.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    When you quit, you fail. The surest way to lose at any endeavor is to quit. But fatigue, discomfort, and discouragement are merely symptoms of effort.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Trust your instincts. What good is intuition if you let second-guessing drown it out? The worst enemy of success is self-doubt.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Learn something new every day. Have the mindset of a student. Never think you are too old to ask questions or know too much to learn something new.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Make what is valuable important. Instead of thinking about what is profitable, think about what is valuable. Invest in others and you will grow your portfolio.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Lolly Daskal, inc.com">
    Believe in yourself. The way you see yourself is the way you will treat yourself, and the way you treat yourself is what you become.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Hamilton Boudreaux">
    Observe the space between your thoughts, then observe the observer.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jon Kabat-Zinn">
    The best way to capture moments is to pay attention. This is how we cultivate mindfulness. Mindfulness means being awake. It means knowing what you are doing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Wilson Mizner">
    Don't talk about yourself; it will be done when you leave.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Immanuel Kant">
    To be is to do.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Logan Pearsall Smith">
    It takes a great man to give sound advice tactfully, but a greater to accept it graciously.
  </quote>
  <quote source="James Huneker">
    Great art is an instant arrested in eternity.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Oscar Levant">
    Roses are red, violets are blue, I'm schizophrenic, and so am I.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Jessamyn West">
  The past is really almost as much a work of the imagination as the future. 
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  True happiness is... to enjoy the present, without anxious dependence upon the future.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  A gem cannot be polished without friction, nor a man perfected without trials.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  There is no person so severely punished, as those who subject themselves to the whip of their own remorse.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  No man was ever wise by chance.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  Religion is regarded by the common people as true, by the wise as false, and by the rulers as useful.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  Be not too hasty either with praise or blame; speak always as though you were giving evidence before the judgement-seat of the Gods.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Seneca">
  Be silent as to services you have rendered, but speak of favours you have received.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  I can do anything. It's a simple phrase, but it helps to remind yourself — you really can do anything you set your mind to.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  You deserve a better life — whether that means a better job, a healthier body or more money. Work for it.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  It's never too late. No matter how old you are or how many opportunities you've passed up before, it's never too late to make a decision and get a fresh start.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  There will always be challenges. No matter what you do in life, there will always be challenges — don't let one set get the better of you.
  </quote>
  <quote source=" Joachim I. Krueger">
  When Life Issues an Invitation, Accept  - Spontaneity is the best antidote to fear and habit. 
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  There's no "perfect" time. If you're waiting for the perfect moment, forget about it — there's no such thing.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  There's no perfect plan. There are some definite flaws in your plan — but there are in every plan.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Entrepreneur.com">
  Everybody starts somewhere. Nobody is born successful. Everyone starts somewhere, and usually from the bottom.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
  Honor those who seek the truth, beware of those who’ve found it.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
  Enlightenment is the space between your thoughts.
  </quote>
  <quote source="Anonymous">
  Be yourself. Everyone else is taken.
  </quote>
</quotes>

